

Héloïse Mazingarbe

My ideal job in 3 words: Meaning, Responsibility, Team

From January 2021

After a 2-year contract in a Web agency as a Webmarketing Project Manager in Budapest, I became a Back-End Developer in a scale-up (18 months) to gain more technical skills.

French (native) - English (fluent) - Spanish (intermediary) +33 6 74 24 20 28 - heloise.mazingarbe@gmail.com (27 years old)

Work Experience

Jaimy by Belfius, Ruby on Rails Back-End Developer

Brussels (BE), May 2019 ~ Dec 2020

- Developing new functionalities for jaimy.be, pro.jaimy.be and the internal Back-Office
- Setting up external APIs (Twilio, Segment, Teamleader, Google Ads API...)
- Test and Learn: solving bugs, refactoring existing code, writing RSpecs
- Working together as a team (Github, Jira, Agile Method, Reviews, Communication with the Front-End)

AEP Digital, Webmarketing Project Manager

Budapest (HU), Jan 2017 ~ Dec 2018

- Managing the webmarketing strategy of a dozen of clients: Monthly calling appointments
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO): Content creation, backlinks optimizations, SEO audits
- Search Engine Marketing (SEM): Google Ads campaigns creation, SEM audits
- Social Media Optimization (SMO): Media strategy on Facebook Ads, Linkedin Ads and Twitter Ads

Popcarte, Web editor & Webmarketing assistant

Barcelona (ES), Jul 2015 ~ Dec 2015

- Writing Web content, managing the blog & setting up SEO recommendations
- Community Management: animating social networks (Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Google +)

Education

Le Wagon, Programming

Lille (FR), Jan 2019 ~ Mar 2019

- 9-week intensive coding bootcamp: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails
- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of https://just-play.live

Audencia Business School, Master's Degree, Digital Marketing

Nantes (FR), Sep 2013 ~ Jun 2017

- Studied basics of finance, accounting, marketing, human resources and strategy
- Study semester abroad in Hong Kong (HK) specialization in IT

Skills

Webmarketing

Webinarketing

Specific tools management for analysis & performance support - Web strategy development

Back-End Development Ruby on Rails -Database with PostgreSQL - Basics of JavaScript / HTML / CSS

Soft Skills